https://www.canvasetc.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Canvas ETC
Fabric Swatches Click Here
Printed Fabric Samples
Nonwoven material, nose clips, elastic and more
Custom Slitting, Sewing and On-demand Fabric Printing now available! Call 404-514-7166
Start typing and press Enter to search
Login
Join
0
No products in the cart.
ShopAirocideArtist Canvas Painting RollsLinen CanvasPre Primed Canvas Floor ClothPrimed Painters CanvasUnprimed CanvasCanvas Fabric Duck Cloth#1 Cotton Duck#10 Cotton Duck#12 Cotton Duck Canvas#4 Cotton Duck#6 Duck Canvas#8 Cotton Duck10 oz Cotton Duck Fabric7 oz Duck ClothArmy Duck FabricBoat Cover CanvasBull DenimCanvak Wax CompoundCanvas ColorsCorn Hole Game FabricHeavyweight CottonMil SpecMuslin FabricOrganic Cotton FabricSlipcover Fabric (duck)Sunforger CanvasTwill FabricUpholstery FabricWaxed CanvasCovid 19 SuppliesDenier Fabric1000 Denier Nylon1050 Denier Ballistic Material1680D Ballistic Fabric210D Oxford Cloth420D Nylon Packcloth600D Polyester70 Denier Nylon RipstopAwning CanvasBerry Amendment Compliant FabricsCamo FabricsCordura Fabric by the yardFleece & Napped FabricsLightweight Tent MaterialMosquito Repellent Mesh NettingNo See Um NettingNon Woven PolypropylenePolyester Mesh FabricPolyester Vinyl FabricFabric PrintingJWylie DesignsKatja Ollendorff DesignsLulet DesignsPop Up Canopy TentPrint Your Own DesignFabric ScrapsFree Sewing TutorialsHeat Resistant FabricHeavy Duty TarpsCanvas TarpsLightweight Flatbed TarpsStandard Flatbed TarpsSteel TarpsTruck TarpsInsulated FabricKhadiKhadi BooksKhadi PacksKhadi SheetsMass Loaded VinylPersonal Protective Equipment PPEPipe and DrapeBasesDrape SupportFlame Retardant FabricPanel DrapesPipe & Drape 2.0 by VersatopPipe and Drape Hardware AccessoriesPipe and Drape KitsPipe and Drape StorageStep and RepeatTable SkirtingThe Posh AcademyUprightsRecasens Sunbrella Type FabricSewing AccessoriesAluminum Nose ClipsAustriAlpin Cobra BuckleHook and LoopKong CarabinerMilitary WebbingNylon Bonded ThreadPolyester Bonded ThreadPolypro WebbingSide Release BucklesZippersTote Bags & Finished GoodsMoving BlanketsUtility BagsTrade Show DisplaysBanner StandsTrade Show BannersTrade Show Booth DisplaysTrade Show TableclothsTrue Timber CamoVermiculite Insulation Fabric
About Us
Tutorials
Blog
Contact Us
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Canvasetc knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Canvasetc, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Canvasetc Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Canvasetc. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your “Subscription” preferences by logging into your account.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
Does Canvasetc Share the Information It Receives?
We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the “log off” link located in the side menu.
Which Information Can I Access?
Canvasetc gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Canvasetc, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the “Contact Us” link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to Canvasetc. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.
Automatic Information
For security purposes Canvasetc sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.
Questions
Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the “Contact Us” link in the side menu. Or you can email us at: cs@canvasetc.com
Quick Links
About Us – Largest Online Fabric Store
Airocide
Blog
Cart
Checkout
Contact Us
Home Page – Canvas Fabric & Online Fabric Store
What is Duck Cloth?
